In school, kids are told to drink water in class, tannoy announcers encourage us to remember our bottles on public transport, and we're reminded by experts that water will help us have glowing skin and regulate our weight.
在学校里，孩子们被告知要在课堂上喝水，公共广播播音员鼓励我们搭乘公共交通工具时记得带水壶，专家们也提醒我们，水能帮助我们拥有光彩照人的皮肤并调节体重。
But how much should we actually be drinking?
但我们到底应该喝多少呢？
For many years, people have followed the unofficial advice of drinking eight glasses of water, eight times a day, known as the '8x8 rule'.
多年来，人们一直遵循每天喝八杯水、每日八次的非官方建议，即所谓的"8x8法则"。
According to Jessica Brown, writing for BBC Future, this seems to have partly come from not understanding guidance that was published almost 80 years ago.
为BBC Future撰稿的杰西卡·布朗表示，这似乎部分源于对近80年前发布的指南的误解。
In 1945, the US Food and Nutrition Board of National Research Council advised drinking one millilitre of liquid for every recommended calorie of food.
1945年，美国国家研究委员会食品与营养委员会建议，每摄入一卡路里推荐食物，就应饮用一毫升水。
This is equivalent to around two litres of water a day, or eight glasses per person.
这相当于每人每天大约两升水，或八杯水。
But, Jessica says, the reality is that individuals have different needs.
但是，杰西卡说，现实是每个人都有不同的需求。
Weight, age and activity level all affect how much water someone should drink.
体重、年龄和活动水平都会影响一个人应该喝多少水。
So, should we control our water intake at all?
那么，我们到底是否应该控制水摄入量？
It's not that important, according to Dr Stanley Goldfarb from the University of Pennsylvania.
宾夕法尼亚大学的斯坦利·戈德法布博士说，这并不那么重要。
He told BBC podcast More or Less that our body is very good at hydration control – it tells us when we are dehydrated.
他告诉BBC播客《或多或少》节目，我们的身体非常擅长水分调节——它会在我们脱水时告诉我们。
First, there is "the thirst system, which tells us go drink because your body water content is slightly reduced.
首先，有"口渴系统，它会告诉我们去喝水，因为你体内的水分含量轻微减少了。
And secondly, we have the kidney system, which helps to retain any water and kicks in well before we really sense any thirst".
其次，我们有肾脏系统，它有助于保留水分，并且在我们真正感到口渴之前就开始起作用了"。
There are, of course, benefits to drinking water.
当然，喝水有好处。
It helps our bodies regulate temperature, flushes out toxins, aids digestion and acts as a shock absorber for our joints.
它帮助我们的身体调节体温，排出毒素，促进消化，并充当关节的减震器。
It also contains essential nutrients like calcium and magnesium, which are important for bone strength.
它还含有必需的营养素，如钙和镁，这对骨骼强度很重要。
So, next time you feel thirsty, reach for a glass of water, but otherwise, don't worry about it!
所以，下次你感到口渴时，伸手去拿杯水，但其他时候，就别担心了！
Your body knows what it's doing.
你的身体知道它在做什么。